Yena Lee

PROFILE

Self-motivated, diligent 3rd year student at the University of Toronto, specializing in Computer Science with a focus on Software Engineering. Extracurricular experiences demonstrating the ability to communicate and collaborate with a team. Demonstrated hardworking skill, open to work with new skills.

EXPERIENCE

Paradigm (Student Inventing Club)

October 2016 - May 2017

NGO LifeWorld, KEDCO (Korea Economic Development Cooperative)

- Problem-solving skills used to the invention called 'RF Security Necklace,' submitted to Design Thinking Youth Inventors Challenge and received a grand prize.
- Solid collaborative skills used in working with Chief Director of KEDCO and NGO LifeWorld, developed and printed prototypes of the invention.
- Intermediate persuasive skills used in fundraising session at "Happy Bean" and the school concert, achieving the goal of 7,000 CAD.
- Robust leadership and communication skill used in the science and hygiene education at Holy Child's School, Paul's Home, and Thapathali community.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

English Tutoring, Teacher

June 2020 – Present

Seoul, South Korea

 Demonstrated written and oral communication skills through remotely providing English tutoring to a grade 9 girl, helping to build up reading, writing, and speaking skills.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Math in Motion Girls in Gear (MiMGiG), Volunteer

November 2019

University of Toronto Scarborough, Canada

 Demonstrated leadership and oral communication skill through volunteering at the annual conference of MiMGiG and encouraging grade 9 girls in mathematics, giving assistant during mathematics sessions.

Basketball Team, Team Player of Varsity A

November 2012 - March 2018

BHA (Branksome Hall Asia), Jeju, South Korea

Performed collaboration and oral communication skills as a
position of point guard and small forward, winning the second
place in JISAC and the second place in KISAC tournament in
2018.

DETAILS

33, Hyoryeong-Ro 68-Gil, Seocho-Gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea, 06723 +82(10) 9061-6986 leeyena.lee@mail.utoronto.ca

SKILLS

Python and C MS Excel Illustrator and Photoshop Problem-Solving Collaborative Skill Hardworking Skill Positive Attitude Korean **Fnglish**

EDUCATION

Candidate, Honors Bachelor of Science

September 2018 – Present
University of Toronto Scarborough –
Specialist (Co-operative) Program in
Computer

AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

- Math in Motion Girls in Gear Certificate of Appreciation November 2019
- Dean's List
 October 2019
- Google Cloud Platform Essentials

October 2019

- Ontario College's Athletic Association Basketball Tournament 1st Place November 2018
- Teenager Engineering Idea Contest Grand Prize Certificate January 2017